mydonedone.com 2013-08-08

# Privacy Policy - DoneDone

## Information Gathering and Usage

We Are Mammoth may collect data from you that you provide to us voluntarily, such as your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, and other personal information. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web site, productions, services, and programs to the public, suppliers, and our clients, and may be used to contact you via e-mail or by regular mail, and to provide you with information that we believe to be of interest to you. The information you share with We Are Mammoth through the Service or any other services provided by We Are Mammoth is not shared with or sold to other people or organizations for commercial purposes, except when you have permitted us to do so in order to provide products or services you’ve requested.

## Transfer of Information Outside We Are Mammoth

Your information may be accessible to one or more of our vendors who provide services that support our business. We do not sell or transfer the information you send to us to others outside of our company, except that your data may be transferred to an outside vendor during the normal course of system backups or application maintenance and development. Our vendors are prohibited from using or selling your personal data for any purposes other than to support We Are Mammoth. The collected information will be shared with a 3rd party in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service or as otherwise requested by law. We may transfer information about you if We Are Mammoth or DoneDone is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, We Are Mammoth will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## Data Storage

We Are Mammoth uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run DoneDone. Although We Are Mammoth owns the code, databases, and all rights to the DoneDone application, you retain all rights to your data.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are required to use the DoneDone service. We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies. You are required to log-in to your DoneDone Site after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.

## Disclosure

We Are Mammoth may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.

## Changes

We Are Mammoth may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your DoneDone primary account holder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

## Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be emailed to [feedback@mydonedone.com](mailto:feedback@mydonedone.com?subject=Questions%20regarding%20DoneDone%20Privacy%20Policy) or by mail at We Are Mammoth 210 N. Morgan St. Chicago, IL 60607 (ATTN: DoneDone Privacy Policy).

## Be sure to read our Terms of Use >
